[
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "Calculate the limit as x approaches 1/2 of (12x^2+8x-7)/(2x^2-19x+9)",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "-20/17",
      "-8/19",
      "-85",
      "DNE "
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "Find the limit as x approaches 1 of f(x) if f(x) = (x^2+4) when x != 1 and 2 when x = 1.",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "2",
      "5",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "Find the limit as x approaches 2pi of cos(x)csc^2(x) - cos^3(x)csc^2(x)",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "-1",
      "0",
      "1",
      "DNE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "Find the limit as x approaches 0 of -x/(sqrt(x+9)-3)",
    "correct_answer": 1,
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "-6",
      "6",
      "DNE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "Given the limit as x approaches 0 of f(x) is 9, the limit as x approaches 0 of g(x) is -9, and the limit as x approaches 9 of h(x) is 5, find the limit as x approaches 0 of g(x)/(h(x)-f(x))",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "-9/14",
      "9/14",
      "9/4",
      "DNE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "If f(x) = -13ln(x) + 7x^3 + 4x^2 + sin(x) and g(x) = ln(x^2) - 42x^3 + 3x^2 - sin(x), find the limit as x approaches infinity of f(x)/g(x)",
    "correct_answer": 1,
    "answers": [
      "-13/2",
      "-1/6",
      "-1",
      "4/3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "Find the limit as x approaches 0 of x/sin(3x)",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "1/3",
      " 3",
      " 0",
      " DNE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "Find the limit as x approaches 0 of (1-cos^2(x))/x",
    "correct_answer": 1,
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "infinity",
      "DNE"
    ]
  },{
  "class_name": "Calculus AB",
  "unit": "2",
  "question": "Given f(x) = 7/x^4, find f'(2)",
  "correct_answer": 2,
  "answers": [
    "-14",
    "-3.5",
    "-.875",
    "-1.75"
  ]
},
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "2",
    "question": "Given f(x) = (x^2 - 4x + 2)(2x^3 - x2 + 4), find f'(x)",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "10x^4 - 36x^3 + 24x^2 + 4x - 16",
      "2x^4 - 32x^3 + 24x^2 + 4x - 16",
      "2x^4 - 36x^3 + 24x^2 + 4x - 16",
      "10x^4 - 32x^3 + 24^x2 + 4x - 16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "2",
    "question": "Find the equation for the tangent line to the curve y = x^2 - x at x = 3",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "y = -7x + 6",
      "y = -7x - 6",
      "y = -7x - 9",
      "y = -7x + 9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "2",
    "question": "Find the value(s) of x such that the tangent line to the curve y = x^3 - 12x + 2 is horizontal",
    "correct_answer": 3,
    "answers": [
      "-2,0,2",
      "0",
      "0,2",
      "2,-2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "2",
    "question": "If g\u2032(3) = 4 and h\u2032(3) = -1, find f\u2032(3) where f(x) = 5g(x) + 3h(x) + 2",
    "correct_answer": 1,
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "17",
      "23",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "2",
    "question": "Find f'(0) if f(x) = tan(x)/(2x-3)",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "-1/3",
      "1/9",
      "0",
      "DNE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "2",
    "question": "Find f'(x) if f(x) = sec(8x)",
    "correct_answer": 3,
    "answers": [
      "8sec(8x)cot(8x)",
      "8sec(x)tan(x)",
      "-sec(8x)tan(8x)",
      "8sec(8x)tan(8x)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "class_name": "Calculus AB",
    "unit": "2",
    "question": "Find dy/dx if 2xy - y^2 = 1",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "x/(y-x)",
      "x/(x-y)",
      "y/(y-x)",
      "y(x-y)"
    ]
  }
]